Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there?
Hold on for me!
On this long journey that
we've only barely begun!
Friendship, love, courage,
and a little bit of fun!
These are the things.
That even as the years go by!
Will not ever vanish from our minds!
We are all pieces of
a single planet Earth!
Little by little we can
find each other's worth!
And as we see!
What sort of form we're meant to take!
All of us know the wind will
always keep on blowing away!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you!
As you finish what you've begun!
Look through that wind to dry!
All the tears as you're bleeding!
The things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure!
Found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there!
Hold on for me!
All the tears you shed will help
you to become so much stronger!
All the tears you shed
will help you to remember!
Everything, everything, everything!
Now and forever!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, yay!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you
as you finish what you've begun!
Let's do that wind to dry all the tears as
you're blaving the
things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure,
found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there!
Hold on for me!
The government knows me as the
pirate who hates other pirates!
An accurate assessment!
Excluding your people!
Really?
You hate pirates?
That must be a shock coming from me
I used to visit Whitebeard's
ship on a regular basis,
but because of my status
with the government,
I'd travel underwater to get there.
Even so, he and his crew
were good friends to me.
That's so.
Well, I recall you almost
killed me one time.
I suppose I can say the
same thing about you.
But all that aside, I owe
Whitebeard a great debt.
Fishman Island is now a
peaceful haven once again
and it's all thanks to
that old man of yours.
As you know pirates sailing along
the Grand Line must pass through
Fishman Island to reach the New World
so not long after the dawn of the
great pirate era the island was in
trouble numerous human pirates and
navy ships that were chasing after
Whitebeard arrived there wreaking havoc.
Countless fishmen and mermaids
were kidnapped and sold as slaves.
And just when despair
threatened to conquer our hearts
Whitebeard showed himself.
From this point forward I claim
this island as my territory.
A simple proclamation A
precious few words ensured
that no one would lay a finger
on Fishman Island again.
The power that Whitebeard
commands is that great.
As long as I live, I will
never forget that day.
Not just my homeland.
He protects other islands
in much the same manner.
The government targets him because he is a
pirate, but they refuse to see the truth.
That is why I object.
If he happened to die, what
would become of the sea?
Who would dare to welcome the chaos
that would reign in his absence?
Who but a fool would dare
to usher in such madness?
I want to stop this war even
if I must give up my life.
I wanted to rescue you, Ace.
But I failed.
Jinbei, please.
That's enough.
This is painful.
Even so, I haven't given up hope yet.
I believe that a miracle
and our chance may come.
My my,
sounds like there's a lot of
fun going on in the world.
This is a now or never
opportunity to defeat. Whitebeard.
Even locked down here, I can't
help but feel a bit excited.
How dare you!
Oh yeah, you think you
can take the old man?
Not just me.
Kill him!
They're gonna kill Whitebeard!
About time!
Take him out!
You gotta let me out of here!
I wanna be the one to
kill him! Let me out!
I wanna take a crack at him too!
I'm gonna put an end to his era.
Fools! Silence!
Shinobu, Ace, look, do you get it?
This world is full of
dozens of second-placers,
silver medalists who could never
defeat Roger and Whitebeard,
all holding back their tears.
No wonder we lost
communication with Level 2.
Those prisoners knocked a
basilisk right into the comm room.
Those two were able to beat a basilisk?
Where the hell are they anyway?
And what is going on down there?
Wait, hold on.
There they are.
I've got them.
You do? Really? Yes, sir.
But now it seems there are three of them.
There's what?
The big centipede just exploded
into a bunch of little ones!
What centipede?
It was a bunch of poisonous puzzle
scorpions stacked on top of one another!
Now there are more things chasing us!
That's why I'm the best while those dumb
animals are following my footsteps we're
free to make our
Break damn
these things
by the way I heard the boss of beasts
on level two looks like some sort Of lion
are all of these things bosses of course
they're not bosses these are clearly
manticores Can't you see their human faces?
And if they catch us, they'll
chew until only bones remain.
That's harsh.
Get the key in.
Give me the key. Ignore them.
Since they have human faces,
they can imitate different people
they've heard around the prison.
Help me. Please.
It's too painful.
They're just repeating things they've
heard some of the prisoners say.
They have no idea what it means.
This sure is creepy.
Loin cloth. Loin cloth.
Strawberry panties.
What the hell have they been
listening to around here?
Beefsteak, beefsteak, beefsteak!
Beefsteak?
Yeah, listen to them!
Hey! Hey, you!
You said you were going to help
us get through this place, right?
Of course I did, and I meant it.
We should join forces and break
out of this prison together.
What do you say?
I told you, I don't want to break out.
I want to know how to
get down to level three.
Huh?
I'm afraid you don't
understand the situation.
I assure you, it only gets
worse the deeper you go.
Here's the scoop.
Straw Hat broke into the prison
to rescue his brother Ace.
Are you seriously telling me
Firefist Ace is Straw Hat's brother?
I never knew.
And you broke into Impel
Down to rescue him?
I'm running out of time.
If someone like Firefist
Ace is being held here,
then he would be all the
way down in level five.
He wants to go there.
No way. Call me out. That's madness.
I wouldn't dare.
Wait.
Look.
I get that you don't want to join us.
Fine.
But how do we get there?
Use the stairs, you imbecile!
Oh, wait a second.
The stairs are all connected
from level one to level three.
I could use Straw Hat
as bait for the beast
guarding the stairs if it makes my escape.
Yes, that's good.
Why, it's ingenious, Ethan.
No, I'll stay. Let's go together.
You can count on me, Straw Hat!
It's this way, Abe!
Oh crap, you ran into something big!
It's the guardian of the stairs
to help each notice the sinks!
Is that a lion or a grandpa?
Oh my god!
Stay! I'm close!
Cover it back to you!
Noodle.
What?
Noodle?!
Pork Noodle!
Chinese Noodle!
Were the prisoners really
talking about noodles that much?
Vegetable Noodle!
Hot Men!
You mean me?
This thing's tough!
That's gotta be the space and
he's going crazy about something.
I knew it.
I just knew it.
We're gonna be stuck
in this place forever.
Damn it.
His strong end making me hungry. Yeah.
You know to be honest.
I have no interest in going down
to the lower levels of this place.
I'm right there with you on that one.
Good.
Now what do you say we form an
alliance and break out of this dump?
I'm so pleased to hear
that you're a real escapee.
Now that that's settled, let's
begin the Straw Hat for dinner plan.
Hey, what are you two doing? Let's move!
Here he comes!
Look out!
Now, come, come!
Fartouca!
What are you doing?
How's it a good idea to piss him off?
Someone!
That's not fair.
Why can't I go to a
higher safer place, too?
Corn!
You know, corn!
I tricked you, you ghastly abomination.
What you smashed was just a wax figure.
I created with my wax wax power.
Huxing noodle.
Though I admit they look much more
convincing With Miss Goldenwing's coloring.
But it was still enough to trick
A foolish beast such as yourself!
Think you can tell?
Which one is the real me?
Noodle Missed me?
Noodle Missed again.
No, no. Wrong. Try again.
Ha!
That looks fun!
Get him!
Get him! No, no. Not even close. No, no.
I don't even try. Missed again.
You're bad at this.
Oh, man.
Try there! No, no. Missed again.
No, no. Yeah! Get him! No, no.
He's playing with him. What the hell?
I know you're a risk-taker, kid,
but you're gonna laugh
yourself into an early grave.
Seems like you're starting
to get the hang of this.
Let the simpletons have their fun.
Now's my chance to make a break for it.
Hey, what's that rumbling
and shaking all about?
Holy crap, those three guys must
really be pissing off the Sphinx.
No!
What's happening?
I don't know, but I don't like it.
Level 3 to monitoring room.
We're hearing a lot of
noise from upstairs.
Mr.
3, it's time to fly
The perfect escape plan, huh?
This wasn't our plan, we're just running
Works either way, I guess Hey, look,
that must be the door that needs to
the stairs I'll make a key out of wax
Yes,
this is the monitoring room Look,
we still can't get in
touch with level 2 so
we have no idea what's
going on down there.
No, no, no, you stupid beast!
You've cracked the floor!
Now we're all gonna...
This is level three!
Oh, the ceiling is giving way!
The Sphinx is...
Oh, no!
Damn it all!
We're falling to level three!
Noodle!
Mara da room, we've arrived at level two!
Can you see the image on screen?
We can.
Keep us posted on what
you find down there.
Roger that.
Look at the size of this hole!
It's so big even the sphinx
could have fallen through it!
What in the hell is Straw
Hat Luffy looking for?
That does not look good.
I don't know how they got the keys.
But the prisoners on level
two are out of their cells.
Don't tell me Straw Hat
and his friends did this.
Those guards are in trouble down.
there.
Let's hear it for our
savior, Captain Buggy.
Now it's payback time.
Level two reporting in.
We need backup here.
The prisoners are all free.
I repeat, the prisoners are all free.
Quick, let's go to level two.
Hey, good news, men.
We know what Straw Hat's doing. Yeah?
Who told
I told you, Fleet Admiral Sengoku
himself just sent word to us.
Little did we know, Monkey D.
Luffy and our condemned
prisoner Port Gosti Ace
have more in common than
the D in their names.
It turns out they're brothers!
Hold on!
Are you saying he's trying
to stop the public execution?
Break in and make it out with his
brother before we can transport him?
What else could it be?
That would explain why
he keeps going down.
We were so focused on Whitebeard's
attack, we let him sneak inside.
If he manages to pull this off,
all hell's gonna break loose.
We've got to stop him.
Inform Warden Magellan immediately and get
that riot on level two under control. Now
think
this is funny?
We're at a crossroads that could
change the future of the sea.
Yet that troublemaking grandson of yours
seems to undermine our
efforts at every turn.
Just like it Enies Lobby.
Then the Celestial Dragons.
Dammit!
This is unprecedented, I say.
Let this sink in.
We haven't had a single breakout
in Impel Down in the past 20 years.
The Golden Lion was the last.
No one else has challenged these
walls from the inside or the outside.
Impel Down is more than a prison.
It's a symbol of unyielding
justice with an iron-tight
reputation that Straw Hat
is attempting to tarnish.
And to make it even worse,
he's the grandson of a marine!
And Mrs.
Boy, I'm so proud of him!
Uh, damn that Kuma.
He said he took care of the Straw
Hat crew at the Sabahodi Archipelago.
I should have known better
than to trust that fool.
Man's one of the seven
warlords of the sea.
What do you expect?
What I want to know is how he was able to
get through the defenses we've got set up.
You think you flew here?
That's enough!
If you weren't known all over the
Grand Line as the hero of the Navy,
Doc, I'd make you take responsibility
for your family myself!
Go ahead. Lock me up. Execute me.
It won't change a thing.
Nothing.
You hear me?
It's too late.
Laugh it up while you can.
But a blow like this to our reputation
will have serious repercussions.
City and I have tried to keep this under
wraps, but there's only so much we can do.
Hey, those are mine, damn it.
No fair. Get up already.
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
This floor feels like a frying pan!
So are we in the desert?
It's hot.
Why is it so quiet?
Level three.
Oh, I never wanted to end up here.
If I have to go to one more crappy
place with you, I'll lose my mind.
He's taking a cat now.
Oh, that's real funny.
This place is especially
bad for someone like me.
I'm a wax man, after all.
Well, all right, then off we go.
Hey look it's grilled
chicken time that is not
natural a hummingbird
fluttered down from above.
It was grilled in the
open how hot is it here?
Hey could you tell me where the
A miserable sight if
i've ever seen one you
wouldn't think looking at
them now but the Prisoners
on this floor were all hardened criminals
commanding bounties of
over 50 million berries
Beneath here is the burning heat hell
cooking the ground also these men are
deprived of food And water leaving them
half dead a shell of their former selves
This is level three the starvation hell
Yes now you know why this floor is
covered with what appears to be sand
Alas yes chances are what
you're standing on are
the remains of prisoners
who have Completely dried
up if we remain in this
place too long we'll become
sand beneath Someone's
feet just like they did
In other words let's move while we have
the sweat to spare okay then let's go
To level four already seriously not that
way we need to take the stairs to the
left. We do?
No, we should take the pass on the right.
Are you making this up?
Why?
Why are we back
where we started?
It's hot here.
I sure hope we get to level four soon.
Go by yourself.
I'm getting out of here.
But you said we were going
to say these together.
You have to show me the way.
That was the deal.
I never said that.
Neither of us did.
You're just making stuff up because
that's what What do you want to hear?
I've sworn you said that.
They've returned and are in place, sir.
Good.
Then draw the net. Yes, sir!
Fine, I don't need...
What is this thing? A trap? Obviously.
Damn it, we're done for.
I think it's made of fire.
What's with this?
I should be able to use
my chop-chop powers.
This must be lined with sea prism stone.
I fear they'll give us more than a slap on
the wrist for our little attempted escape.
We'll be tortured to death.
We've captured the invader straw
hat Luffy, along with two others.
What do you mean, two others?
I got a name.
Don't antagonize them, buggy.
You'll only make it worse.
And it's more than bad
enough already. WRAP!
There's gotta be some way to rip this net!
The guards and the Bligori are coming!
Put the Sea Prism Stone handcuffs on them!
Yes, sir!
Who's this guy?
This guy is called Solbreath.
Solbreath, huh?
You better change your diet.
No, that's not what I said.
Pay attention. It's saw death.
Got it right
Sardine head no get it right.
What's wrong with you?
At any rate.
There's no point in you resisting
us you're in a highly secure
underwater prison so needless to
say there's nowhere for you to run!
You know you're fortunate that I
was the one who captured you there
are four other guards prowling
around on the floors beyond this one?
And they're demons.
He's right.
This little guy's downright cute
compared to what's down there.
Chief the Sphinx!
He's moved on to busters now!
Oh no!
He's gonna break the net!
Be careful, men!
They can't escape,
especially not Straw Hat!
Did he say that one yet?
I don't even care anymore!
Hey, I'm free!
It's still hot, but at
least they can run away.
After them.
Oh, Sackler!
Hey, where'd they go?
Come on, Mr.
Three, hurry up I can't
move quickly in this heat.
They climbed up the net, good thinking!
So long, Straw Hat.
Tell your brother I said hello.
If he's still alive, I'll buy him a drink.
And by the way, thanks for being
our live bait, you little imbecile!
Glad to see they're safe.
Well, okay. See ya.
Thanks a lot for your help, you guys.
He's so sweet.
My heart, it's breaking.
Stay sharp, men.
He's got a 300 million berry bounty.
This is our chance. Run for it.
Right, let's go.
Look, I don't have time to
fight all you guys right now.
Show them all.
Oh, great!
He's on a rampage!
He's on the run! After him!
The stairs to go down!
Too hot!
I think we're safe up here.
Their attention's on
Straw Hat like we planned.
They've sealed off the
staircases leading up,
and it's getting far too hot for
me to remain here any longer.
Hey, who's that singing?
They always say it's all
about the ways of boys
and girls but I'm special
cause I take the best
from both worlds that's
why we are always free
always free when you're
queer you never fear No,
never fear Oh, come my way
Oh, come my way
Keep it up,
boys Spin and spin like you're caught
up at the time of the times Hurry,
this way Wait,
listen I don't think we should
Come on,
lazybones The party's just getting started
If you think it's steamy in here now,
you'll really hate it when I'm angry!
Oh, Mr.
Three, how are you?
Well, this is awkward.
What the... Mr. Three!
Wait just a minute here!
What are you doing in Impel Down?
You're behind bars, so you
must have been caught, right?
No, no.
I'm the one who's behind bars, aren't I?
How did you like my
one-of-a-kind double take?
It's a Kenpo special technique called
looking back on that autumn night's dream.
Hey, what the hell is
this strange creature?
Hard to say.
Let's be sure to not let it out.
Oh, don't be mean!
I've got way too much energy
to stay cooped up in here!
Our security here is legendary.
How is he able to slip through?
And though he's just one invader,
if we let him rescue Ace,
not only will it be the ultimate
humiliation for Impel Down,
but for the entire world government!
We can't let that happen!
In the name of Navy Headquarters!
We're gonna head into
that prison And stop,
Straw Hat Luffy, no matter what it takes.
Hold on a moment. Huh?
Who goes there?
I'm Mistress Sadie, our torture expert.
We've already been compromised,
so accepting the help of the
Navy would just further disgrace.
Hmm, the good name of Impel Down.
Mistress, really?
What, does she think she's
being cute or something?
I'm adorable!
You will refer to me as Mistress!
Those screams are irresistible!
Why, you... Hold it.
Are you telling me you don't
need the Navy's aid? Yes.
This whole prison is a labyrinthine hell.
If you don't know your way around
in here, you'll be of no help to us.
That being said, if you wish to
serve us, you can guard the outside.
This drawbridge is the only entrance.
We'll secure ourselves inside, raise
it, and seal off Impel Down completely.
We'll do our job.
And as long as you do yours, nobody
will escape from this prison alive.
Fair enough.
We'll remain here and guard the gate then.
There, that's a good boy.
Is that a...
No way.
Koala?
A koala?
Sure is.
Impel Down Impel Down is
now completely sealed off.
And your boo?
Yeah, and Magellan's
here, too What's going on?
You've got a special visitor, Ace!
Behave yourself.
You'll never guess who it is!
Jimbei
You know her well, but
even you've never met her.
Maybe I should give Ace here a hint.
Her name is notorious, but
she never shows herself.
She leads a tribe of
warriors called the Kuja.
And she's one of the
seven warlords of the sea.
Strong, noble, and the most
beautiful woman in the world.
The pirate empress, Boa Hancock!
Yay!
It's Hancock!
Check her out!
Hey, quick question.
When I become warden, will you do me
the honor of being my beautiful bride?
Marry me!
Ouch.
When I'm warden, I'll
hit on her all I want.
I mean, sorry, warden, you
can hit me all you want.
That's enough of your tomfoolery. Woo!
Holy crap.
Guys, am I seeing things?
She's gorgeous.
So she's the snake princess of Kuja.
Hey, move a little closer.
Turn around, Hancock.
Yeah, that is some choice meat.
Hey, hot stuff, come to our cell.
We'll give you some 10-11
like you've never had before.
Well, she smells amazing.
If I ever get out of here, I'm
going straight to Amazon Lily.
I heard it's full of hot, naked chicks.
Count me in.
What is it?
What do you want from me?
Nothing, really.
I simply wanted to take
a good look at you.
To see the cause of the war, I will
take part in firsthand. That's all.
Am I everything you'd hoped for?
Come on, Hancock!
Don't ignore us like that!
Get over here and give me some!
In the past,
you've always been the Empress who stood
her ground and disobeyed every summons.
Yet you're going to take part in this war?
I hope your title is worth your dignity.
A pleasure to meet you, too.
Now mind your foolish tongue.
Oh man, I want to lick her everywhere!
They're trying to talk!
Keep it down, damned louse!
Can it, Magellan!
Or should I say diarrhea man?
Nice one!
Say, Snake Princess, I bet the women on
your island are hungry for guys like us!
Hey, you!
Why don't you make Hannibal
the warden? Really now?
Come on, Hancock, move that sexy
ass over to our cell already!
If you keep accosting me
with those coarse voices...
I'll get scared.
I can't take it.
She's so cute. She's perfect.
Let us have her, Diarrhea Man.
If there's a more vile place in
this world, I don't want to see it.
This makes me sick.
Everyone's calling you Diarrhea
Man, and you just put up with it.
It's disgraceful.
If that's your attitude, I know a
guy who'd love to have your job.
So cute.
Diarrhea Man for shame.
Enough.
She's hot!
Let me have her for myself, diarrhea man!
Diarrhea man!
Let me show her my snake!
I won't tolerate your
impertinence any longer.
This ends now.
Oh!
One Magellan!
Wait a second, please!
You're gonna kill us, too!
You are going to suffer. No! No!
We're dead!
You degenerate seem to
have forgotten your place.
Let me remind you who
the boss is around here.
Wait! What are you doing?
Lord Magellan! Stop! Please! Come on!
We were just joking around! Honest!
No...
you bastard!
You can't do this to me!
Wow, sorry, buddy.
You're a dead man now.
Oh, damn it!
I need the antidote! Help me!
Never forget that I have
not only the authority,
but also the ability to execute
any one of you at my whim.
There!
So sorry about that.
You're free to speak with him now.
Proceed I'm finished here.
Wait is what you just told me the truth?
What reason would I have to lie?
By the way, he was afraid you might
be angry, but he still had to do it
Is that really all you needed?
What do you think they were talking about?
I have no idea.
Honestly, I was busy
trying to get away from you
So ace will you tell me
what she said to you?
she said that my brother is here you mean
luffy the one with the
Straw Hat that you're
always talking about
that fool oh
man when the
heck did i start going
upstairs i want to go
downstairs well if it
started going up it'll
probably go back down
again sooner or later
i'm getting hungry i've
got an image of him
and it appears he's
about to enter district c
All right, we'll see him.
They're using sea prism stone nuts again!
Close one!
Crap, it's that lion thing!
Hey!
Let him go!
Need a hand, pal?
Hey! Zoro!
Ha-ha! Fooled ya!
Swan Parabas!
That is not Zoro, but
he does sound familiar.
Been a while, straw boy.
Did you miss me, old pal?
I think it's about to be turned up!
It's fine!
I'd still rather have Zoro, but I'm glad
you're alive after all that happened!
Dock, open fire on Straw Hat! Yes, sir!
Bastards, you stay away from my friend,
I think you're about to get fed up!
Good boy, Sphinx.
Now, take them out.
There.
After a beating like that, he
shouldn't be bothering us anymore.
Sometimes when you're
dealing with an animal,
you have to teach it
the law of the jungle.
Fried noodles.
You really bailed us out last time,
but I thought for sure you were
dead if I ever happened to see you.
Oh, stop pulling my tail!
You know swans never die!
Unless that isn't true.
And now a reminder of how
Bon Clay's power works.
He ate the clone clone fruit,
allowing him to transform into anyone whose
face he's touched with his right hand.
He was able to turn into Zoro
because he had touched him before,
but he is not able to mimic his strength.
Now there's another escapee to deal with.
The deeper the Straw Hat descends, the
more frenzy seems to pick up along the way.
Lugari, I don't care what it takes.
Don't let them escape.
Oh, and by the way, I heard that you wanted
to go all the way down to level five?
That's the plan, but I can use
a guide if you're not too busy!
Wouldn't have it any other way, my friend!
As fate would have it, there's someone
down on level five I'd like to see, too.
Really?
Now then, shall we go?
Let's do it!